Are you TIRED of the expected?
Rubber is a comedy, drama, fantasy film directed by Quentin Dupieux.
In the California desert, the adventures of a telepathic killer-tire, mysteriously
attracted by a very pretty girl, as witnessed by incredulous onlookers.
Xavier, played by Thomas F. Duffy.
M. Hughes, played by David Bowe.
Chad, played by Stephen Spinella.
Sheila, played by Roxane Mesquida.
Accountant, played by Jack Plotnick.
Man in wheelchair, played by Wings Hauser.
Rubber is a 2010 English-language French independent absurdist horror
comedy film written and directed by Quentin Dupieux.
The film is about a tire that comes to life and uses
psychokinetic powers to kill people.
The film was produced by Realitism Films and had its world premiere at the Critics' Week of
the 2010 Cannes Film Festival, where it received positive reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of exploding building, desert, tire.
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.